# Olha Serediuk

#### Student/freelance copywriter

Energetic and persistent student with 4+ years of experience in research papers. Skilled in financial reporting and copywriting. A leader of best practise who is organised and also has the required number of skills needed to add value to every company. Enthusiastic volunteer.



- kivon2001@gmail.com
- Rivne, Ukraine
- facebook.com/profile.php?id=100011493037883
- +380970335017
- in linkedin.com/in/olha-serediuk-339976236
- instagram.com/wifi\_dog26

## **EDUCATION**

Finance, Banking and Insurance National University of Water and Environmental Engineering

09/2018 - Present

Rivne

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Copywriter and content-maker on social media

Freelance

2018 - Present

Remote

#### Member of external relations department National University of Water and Environmental Engineering

2018 - 2019 Rivne, Ukraine

Achievements/Tasks

 Worked on developing exchange programs for students and managing social events (hackathons, workshops). Promoted student participation in social activities.

#### Young scientist

National University of Water and Environmental Engineering

2018 - Present Rivne

Author of scientific articles and theses. Winner of the Ukrainian competition of student research papers 2021.

#### Volunteer

#### **European Solidarity Corps**

07/2019 - 08/2019 Lublin, Poland

Volunteered in INTERCULTURE 4S: International volunteering for solidarity in the field of city culture for 3 weeks.

Achievements/Tasks

 Got the Youthpass Certificate. The tasks in the project included: helping in organization of big city event - Carnaval Sztukmistrzów; promoting event on social media; working at the information center.

## **SKILLS**

Managerial skills: problem-solving; decision-making; leadership; handling pressure; time management; analytical skills

Communication skills: listening; respect; friendliness

Computer skills: good command of Microsoft Office and Google tools; presentation skills (Prezi); social media promotion

# **ORGANIZATIONS**

"Platskart" Student Organization (2020 - 2021)

Head of "Platskart" Student Organization

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Professional Working Proficiency

French

Elementary Proficiency

# INTERESTS

Additional Activities: volunteering at local or international charity events; learning Chinese at Coursera for HSK1; fitness training; reading fiction and nonfiction.

Seeking in computer hardware systems & components.